Tufts New England Medical Center Planning Office Records UA014
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Loose photographs, 1870 -- 1976; 1960 -- 1970; UA014.001; 1.2 Linear Feet; 470 Digital Object(s)
  - Aerial view of downtown Boston, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03192; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - The Boston Floating Hospital and a neighboring ship docked at a pier, 1900; UA014.001.DO.03193; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Ships; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Boston Floating Hospital; New England Medical Center
  - Men, women, and children waiting in line at an undisclosed location, 1930; UA014.001.DO.03194; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    People; Children; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Entrance of the Tufts School of Medicine and Dentistry, 1967-06; UA014.001.DO.03195; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of Harrison Avenue, 1967-06; UA014.001.DO.03196; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of Harrison Avenue toward Stuart and Harvard Streets, 1967-06; UA014.001.DO.03197; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of Harrison Avenue looking toward the medical center from Stuart Street, 1967-06; UA014.001.DO.03198; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of the South Cove area, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03199; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Aerial photo of the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03200; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of the Tufts-New England Medical Center and the toll road entry on the expressway, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03201; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; New England Medical Center
  - View of the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03202; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of the South Cove area, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03203; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - The view along Charles Street in the South Cove area, 1968; UA014.001.DO.03204; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Area at the corner of Stuart and Carver Streets, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03205; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of Washington Street from Stuart Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03206; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of Park Street Church from Arlington Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03207; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of the Public Garden from Arlington Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03208; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Gardens; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - View up Kneeland Street to the expressway, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03209; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of people walking along Tremont Street from Stuart Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03210; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; People
  - View of Stuart Street with the Statler Hotel in the background, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03211; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Hotels; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Statler Hotel
  - The Music Hall and Wilbur Theatre, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03212; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Theater; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Music Hall Theater; Wilbur Theatre
  - View of construction site and buildings in the South Cove area, 1976-11; UA014.001.DO.03213; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction
  - View down Kneeland Street from Harrison Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03214; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Backyard of housing on Hudson Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03215; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - The Charles Playhouse, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03216; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Theater; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Charles Playhouse
  - The Shubert Theater, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03217; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Theater; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Shubert Theatre
  - St. James' Church, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03218; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Churches; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; St. James' Church
  - Don Bosco Technical High School, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03219; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - The Lincoln School, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03220; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Schools; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Park Square looking toward Copley Square, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03221; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Corner of Arlington Street and Columbus Avenue, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03222; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Park Square looking toward Tremont Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03223; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - The Armory at Columbus Avenue and Arlington St., 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03224; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - The Broadway Boston City Club with the Bradford Hotel in the background, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03225; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Hotels; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Broadway Boston City Club; Bradford Hotel
  - Tremont Street, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03226; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Shawmut Street looking toward the Bradford Hotel, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03227; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Hotels; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Bradford Hotel
  - Looking south from Shawmut Avenue and Broadway Street, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03228; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Tremont Street and the Bradford Hotel, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03229; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of the subway and surrounding buildings in the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03230; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Subways; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Francis E. Shea Square at the corner of Broadway and Tremont Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03231; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Francis E. Shea Square at the corner of Tremont Street and Broadway, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03232; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Arlington Square, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03233; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Tremont Square looking toward the South End, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03234; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Stuart and Arlington Streets looking toward Berkley Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03235; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - The John Hancock Building from St. James Avenue, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03236; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; John Hancock building
  - The Berkley-Clarendon-Stuart Street block, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03237; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Stanhope Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03238; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Buildings and homes along Cortes Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03239; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - The corner of Berkley and Columbus Avenues looking toward Isabelle Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03240; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of the parking lot behind the Music Hall, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03241; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Parking lots
  - Elevated railroad in the South Cove area, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03242; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Railroads; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Corner of Stuart and Kneeland Streets, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03243; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - A row of buildings and homes along a street in the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03244; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - A construction site, 1967; UA014.001.DO.03245; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction
  - Buildings and homes in the South Cove area, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03246; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - A couple walking on the sidewalk along Wahsington Street, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03247; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Kirkland Street, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03248; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - The Bradford Hotel, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03249; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Hotels; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Bradford Hotel
  - Morgan Memorial and Fred H. Seavey Seminary Settlement building, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03250; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Morgan Memorial Goodwill Industries
  - Demolition site on Broadway with the Bradford Hotel and the Don Bosco Technical School in the background, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03251; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Hotels; Schools; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Bradford Hotel; Don Bosco Technical High School
  - Demolition site on Broadway looking toward Washington Street, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03252; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Corner of Oak and Washington Streets, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03253; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Oak Place, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03254; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Aerial photo of the South Cove area, 1962-06; UA014.001.DO.03255; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Boston Floating Hospital, 1962-06; UA014.001.DO.03256; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Buildings that are part of the Boston Floating Hospital, 1962-06; UA014.001.DO.03257; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - An MBTA subway running along side buildings of the Boston Floating Hospital, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03258; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Hospitals; Subways; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Boston Floating Hospital; New England Medical Center
  - The Boston Floating Hospital, 1962-06; UA014.001.DO.03259; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Buildings in the South Cove area, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03260; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Color slide; Image identified only as "Center Building" on the slide.
  - Center hospital of the Tufts School of Medicine on Harrison Avenue, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03261; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Tufts School of Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - Aerial view of the South Cove area and the New England Medical Center, 1962; UA014.001.DO.03262; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Hospitals; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Tufts School of Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - The Pratt Institute, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03263; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Tufts School of Medicine; New England Medical Center; Pratt Institute
  - Rehabilitation Building, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03264; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Tufts School of Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - Posner Hall, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03265; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Tufts School of Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - Bennet Street from Washington Street, 1960; UA014.001.DO.03266; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Sign indicating the location of the New England Medical Center Hospital, 1960; UA014.001.DO.03267; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Signs; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Tufts School of Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - Parking lot in the rear of Posner Hall, 1960; UA014.001.DO.03268; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Dormitories; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Parking lots; Tufts School of Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - Construction on the facade of the Tufts School of Medicine and Dental Medicine, 1960; UA014.001.DO.03269; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Construction; Tufts School of Medicine; School of Dental Medicine; New England Medical Center
  - View of the rear of the Ziskind Laboratory, 1960; UA014.001.DO.03270; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Laboratories; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03271; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03272; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03273; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03274; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of area in the South Cove around Hollis Street, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03275; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03276; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03277; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a parking lot and buildings in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03278; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of a building in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03279; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of buildings and a parking lot near demolition sites in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03280; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Parking lots; Demolition sites
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03281; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the South End Hardware building, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03282; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Buildings; Stores; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; South End Hardware
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03283; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Area in the South Cove near Dore Street, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03284; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the South End Hardware building, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03285; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the South End Hardware building, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03286; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03287; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of buildings in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03288; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of the South End Hardware building, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03289; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Parking lot between Harrison and Tyler Streets, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03290; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Parking lot opposite of the Rehabilitation Building, 1962-07; UA014.001.DO.03291; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Parking lots; New England Medical Center
  - View of a demolition site on Washington Street looking up from Broadway Street toward Bradford Street, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03292; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site on Washington Street between Bennet and Stuart Street, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03293; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of funiture stores along Washington Street, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03294; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Stores; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Demolition site at the corner of Washington and Harvard Streets, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03295; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site, 1968-04; UA014.001.DO.03296; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site from Ash Street looking toward Washington Street, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03297; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site on Washington Street with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1968-07; UA014.001.DO.03298; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Laboratories; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - View of a demolition site on Washington Street looking toward Bennet Street from Stuart Street, 1968-07; UA014.001.DO.03299; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site, 1968-07; UA014.001.DO.03300; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site located behind the Met Theater at the corner of Washington Street and Common Street, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03301; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Theaters; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Met Theatre
  - Demolition site behind the Met Theatre, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03302; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site on Washington Street beyond Common Street looking toward the New England Medical Center, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03303; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition of a parking lot on Washington Street, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03304; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site at the MBTA tunnel located at Bennet and Ash Streets looking toward Washington Street, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03305; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Subways; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - View of a demolition site at Washington Street looking toward the New England Medical Center and Ziskind Laboratory, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03306; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site on Washington Street from Hollis Street, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03307; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site on Washington Street before Bennet Street looking toward the New England Medical Center and the Ziskind Laboratory, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03308; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Ash and Bennet Streets looking toward the New England Medical Center, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03309; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at the corner of Ash and Bennet Streets, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03310; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at the corner of Ash and Bennet Street looking toward Stuart Street, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03311; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at the corner of Ash and Bennet Streets, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03312; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of Bennet Street looking toward Washington Street, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03313; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Washington and Bennet Streets looking toward Stuart Street, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03314; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - People observing a demolition site from a parking lot at Bennet and Washington Streets, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03315; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Demolition site; People; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Demolition site on Washington Street with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03316; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Washington and Hollis Streets looking toward Broadway Street with the Prudential Building in the background, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03317; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Washington Street, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03318; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Washington Street with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03319; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Washington and Bennet Streets looking toward Stuart Street, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03320; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Washington Street, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03321; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Washington and Bennet Streets looking toward the New England Medical Center, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03322; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Washington and Bennet Streets looking toward Stuart Street, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03323; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Ash, Bennet, and Washington Streets with the John Hancock Building in the background, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03324; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; John Hancock building
  - Demolition site at Washington and Bennet Streets looking toward the New England Medical Center and Ziskind Laboratories, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03325; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site at Washington and Bennet Streets from Harvard Street, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03326; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site at Washington and Bennet Streets looking toward Harvard Street, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03327; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03328; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03329; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Cars parked in front of a building in the South Cove area, 1957; UA014.001.DO.03330; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Building in the South Cove area, 1976-11; UA014.001.DO.03350; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site in the South Cove area, 1970; UA014.001.DO.03351; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site in the South Cove area, 1968-10; UA014.001.DO.03352; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site in the South Cove area, 1968; UA014.001.DO.03353; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-11; UA014.001.DO.03354; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site near the MBTA, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03355; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Demolition site; Subways; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - View of construction site in the South Cove area, 1970-06; UA014.001.DO.03356; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03357; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site in the South Cove area, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03358; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction of the Tufts-New England Medical Center, 1972-02; UA014.001.DO.03359; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03360; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03361; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Construction site in the South Cove area, 1969-08; UA014.001.DO.03362; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - T-NEMC Planning Office, 1969; UA014.001.DO.03363; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Rooms; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Interior views; New England Medical Center; Tufts School of Medicine; School of Dental Medicine
  - View of a demolition site at Bennet and Washington Streets from Harvard Street, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03364; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site at Bennet and Washington Streets from Harvard Street with the Don Bosco Technical High School in the background, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03365; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Demolition site; Schools; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Don Bosco Technical High School
  - View of a demolition site at Washington Street from Ash and Bennet Streets with the MBTA subway approaching, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03366; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a demolition site at Washington Street looking toward Bennet Street, 1968-12; UA014.001.DO.03367; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Dental Manpower visit to a demolition site at Bennet Street, 1969-01-08; UA014.001.DO.03368; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    People; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records
  - Dental Manpower visit to a demolition site at Bennet Street, 1969-01-08; UA014.001.DO.03369; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Dental Manpower visit to a demolition site at Bennet Street, 1969-01-18; UA014.001.DO.03370; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Dental Manpower visit to a demolition site at Bennet Street, 1969-01-18; UA014.001.DO.03371; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Dental Manpower visit to a demolition site at Washington and Bennet Streets, 1969-01-18; UA014.001.DO.03372; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at the intersection of Washington, Bennet, and Harvard Streets looking toward Stuart Street, 1969-02; UA014.001.DO.03373; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - Demolition site at Washington and Bennet Streets with the Ziskind Laboratory in the background, 1969-02; UA014.001.DO.03374; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
  - View of a construction site at Washington Street with the John Hancock Building in the background, 1969-02; UA014.001.DO.03375; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; John Hancock building
  - View of a demolition site at the intersection of Bennet, Washington, and Harvard Streets looking toward Don Bosco Technical High School, 1969-02; UA014.001.DO.03376; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
    Views; Buildings; Schools; Demolition site; Tufts New England Medical Center, records; Don Bosco Technical High School
  - View of a demolition site at Washington and Hollis Streets looking toward Stuart Street, 1969-02; UA014.001.DO.03377; Unknown (Box Shared 41)